<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hack It Up</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hack It Up</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing IEEE Standard Academic Papers in Markdown</title>
      <link>/blog/academic-papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/academic-papers/</guid>
      <description>Writing IEEE Standard Academic Papers in Markdown Motivation To have a simple text based system to write academic papers and not worry about the formatting. At the end we could generate a pdf properly formatted as per IEEE standard and works across platforms making the entire setup portable.
 Bring back the focus on writing the content than spending time on formatting the document.
 The Setup Mostly follow up the link to install required software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Real World Alexa Skill</title>
      <link>/blog/alexa-gold-rate-skill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/alexa-gold-rate-skill/</guid>
      <description>Building a Real World Alexa Skill Motivation We all know amazon provides a very good platform to develop skills for its voice assistant Alexa. Getting started on the platform is pretty simple and straight forward following amazon&amp;rsquo;s getting started tutorials.
 Now I wanted to build a real world skill.
 Requirements Requirements that I wanted to achieve
 Get prevailing 22 carat gold prices in India and in some of the major Indian cities Acquire the prices from a dependable source  So there were two main parts to the implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flutter Webview Application</title>
      <link>/blog/flutter-webview-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/flutter-webview-application/</guid>
      <description>Flutter Webview app for a mobile optimized webpage Motivation  My website was built for mobile. It works just fine on a mobile browser. But now I wanted to have an app for the same. Though I had fairly good android development experience, but it was quite sometime ago. And also, lately I had been swarmed with articles about flutter and its usage. So it was time for me to build something with flutter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>